theplayhub.com 2016-06-14

# Privacy Policy - SongsLyrics

Privacy Statement For LyricHub:

LyricHub has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. We want to contribute to providing a safe and secure environment for all users of the internet as a whole and our website in particular.

Information Automatically Logged :  
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site.

Third Party Advertising :  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.

Third Party Cookies :  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

Links :  
LyricHub contains links to other websites. Please observe that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website collecting personally identifiable information.

Acceptance of our Privacy policy :  
Your use of the LyricHub websites signifies your acceptance of this Privacy Policy. If you do not accept the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the LyricHub. This Privacy Policy may be changed from time-to-time without notice. Any such changes will be posted to this web site and will be available for your review. Any continued use of this web site after a change has occurred will constitute your acceptance of such change.

Disclaimer :  
You must agree to the following statement or leave this website. All song lyrics, artist names and images are copyrighted to their respective owners. All Indian song lyrics might be restricted for educational and personal use only.

If you do not agree to all the terms, please disconnect from this site now itself.

This is an information tool provided by at no charge to the user. LyricHub makes no warranties, expressed or implied, for the services we provide. LyricHub will not be held responsible for any damages you or your business may suffer from using LyricHub services.

LyricHub will not be held responsible for any interruptions, delays, failures, inaccuracies, or typographical errors. LyricHub does not represent or warrant that the Service or the server that makes it available, are free of viruses or other harmful components. LyricHub does not warrant or represent that the use or the results of the use of the Service or the materials made available as part of the Service will be correct, accurate, timely, or otherwise reliable.

All files found on this site have been collected from various sources across the web and are believed to be in the “public domain”.

Contacting the Website:  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site or your dealings with this Website, you can contact us
